But do you genuinely feel like if y'all aren't posting certain, if y'all aren't posting somebody that they're not going to work?
If all of us stop talking, and we've actually seen this happen, if we all stop talking about the person, not only will their shit fail, but the people that are hiring them, hoping that they get the press from them, will stop hiring them because you're not getting any pickup.
There's people who literally right now, every platform has their list of who they're not f***ing with.
Some of us share that list.
Okay, are you talking about this, bro?
And sometimes we all just say, okay, we're not going to talk about this person for a while.
And we let it just, and it's just silent.
Unfortunately, the world we live in right now is, if people don't hear or see something every 15 minutes on your social media, on Hollywood Lock, Shea Rimbaud Alert, people lose track.
And they go find something else.
That's why right now, everybody, whether they like it or not, is consumed with Blue Face of Krishan because Zeus has spent a lot of money promoting their shows.
They're on social media all day long, and fans just can't get enough of them, and we can't get enough either.